<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecipesAndCookingTips</string>
    <string-array name="Recipes">
        <item>Cheese Cake</item>
        <item>Cookies</item>
        <item>Crep</item>
        <item>Donuts</item>
        <item>Honuts Cake</item>
        <item>Mochi </item>
        <item>Pan Cake</item>
        <item>Vanilla Ice cream</item>
        <item>Sweet World</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="authors">
        <item>Sweet Greek</item>
        <item>Sweet United States</item>
        <item>Sweet French</item>
        <item>Sweet United States</item>
        <item>Sweet Russian</item>
        <item>Sweet Korean</item>
        <item>Sweet United States</item>
        <item>Sweet World</item>
        <item>Sweet World</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="descriptions">
        <item>the ingredients: one and a half cups of crushed, a quarter cup of melted 16 ounces of cream cheese,one cup of sugar, two eggs, and one teaspoon of vanilla....Combine crushed biscuits and butter for the base. Mix cream cheese, sugar, eggs, and vanilla for the filling. Layer base and filling, bake.  </item>
        <item>the ingredients: 1cup softened butter, 3/4cup of sugar, 3/4cup of brown sugar, 2eggs, 1teaspoon of baking soda, 1/2teaspoon of salt, and 2cups of chocolate ships....Cream butter and sugar, add egg and vanilla. Add flour, baking soda, and salt. Shape into balls, bake. </item>
        <item>the ingredients: 1cup flour, 2 eggs, 1cup milk, a pinch of salt, 1 tablespoon of melted butter..... Note: Sugar is optional, add it if you prefer a sweeter crepe....Combine flour, egg, milk, and salt. Cook on a hot pan. </item>
        <item>the ingredients: 2cups of flour, 4tablespoons of sugar, 2 teaspoons of baking powder, a pinch of salt, 1 egg,1/2cup of melted butter, and oil for frying....Combine flour, yeast, sugar, salt. Add egg, milk, melted butter. Knead, let rise, shape, fry </item>
        <item>the ingredients: 1cup softened butter ,1cup sugar,2 eggs, 1cup honey, 2cups flour, 2teaspoons baking powder, 1/2teaspoon baking soda, 1/2teaspoon cinnamon, 1/2cup milk....Cream butter and sugar, add eggs and vanilla.  Alternately add flour mixture with milk and honey. Bake until done. </item>
        <item>the ingredients: 1 cup water, 1 cup mochi powder (available at Asian grocery stores), sugar to taste (optional), flavorings to taste (vanilla, chocolate, etc.) (optional)....Bring water to a boil, then gradually add mochi powder and sugar (optional), adding your chosen flavours and leave to cool completely. </item>
        <item>the ingredients:1 cup flour, 2 tablespoons sugar, 2 teaspoons baking powder, a pinch of salt, 1 egg, 2 tablespoons melted butter....Combine flour, sugar, baking powder, and salt. Add milk, egg, and melted butter; mix well. Cook on a hot, lightly oiled griddle until golden brown. </item>
        <item>the ingredients: 2cups heavy cream, 1cup whole milk, 3/4cup sugar, 1teaspoon vanilla extract....Mix all ingredients together, then blend in the machine until thick. </item>
        <item>the ingredients:</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>